<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<odoo>
    <report
        id="intern_agreement_letter"
        string="Intern NDA Agreement"
        model="hr.employee"
        report_type="qweb-pdf"
        name="hr_employee_updation.print_intern_agreement_letter"
        file="hr_employee_updation.print_intern_agreement_letter"
        groups="hr.group_hr_manager"
        print_report_name="'Intern Agreement Letter - %s' % (object.name).replace('/', '')"/>

    <template id="print_intern_agreement_letter">
        <t t-call="web.html_container">
            <t t-foreach="docs" t-as="employee">
                <div class="m-5">
                <div style="text-align:right;">
                    <img src="/web/static/src/img/ezest-logo.png?company=${object.company_id.id}" style="margin-left:55px;max-width: 55%;" alt="Company Logo"/>
                </div>
                <div style="color:black;text-align:center;">
                    <h2>Internship Agreement</h2>
                    <h2>(Non-Competition, Non-disclosure and Inventions and Proprietary Information)</h2>
                </div>
                <div class="mt-5">
                <h4>
                    As a condition of my Internship with
                    <strong style="color:black;">
                        e-Zest Solutions Ltd.
                    </strong>
                    ,  its subsidiaries, affiliates, successors, or assigns (together “the Company”), and in consideration of my Internship with the Company and my receipt of the compensation now and hereafter paid to me by the Company, I agree to the following:
                </h4>
                <h2 style="color:black;">
                    A. NONDISCLOSURE of CONFIDENTIAL INFORMATION
                </h2>
                <h2 style="color:black;">
                    1. Company Information
                </h2>
                <h4>
                    I agree at all times during the term of my Internship and thereafter, to hold in strictest confidence, and not to use, except for the benefit of the Company, or to disclose to any person, firm or corporation without written authorization from the 
                    <strong style="color:black;">
                        Leader,
                    </strong>
                    any Confidential Information of the Company. I understand that -“Confidential Information” means any Company proprietary information, technical data, trade secrets or know-how, including but not limited to: research, product plans, products, services, customer lists and customers (including but not limited to: customers of the Company on whom I called or with whom I became acquainted during the term of my Internship), markets, software, and other business information disclosed to me by the Company either directly or indirectly in writing, orally or by drawings or observation of parts or equipment. I further understand that Confidential Information does not include any of the foregoing items which has become publicly known and made generally available through no wrongful act of mine or of others who were under confidentiality obligations as to the item or items involved.
                </h4>
                <h2 style="color:black;">
                    2. Third Party Information
                </h2>
                <h4>
                    I recognize that the Company has received and in the future will receive from third parties their confidential or proprietary information subject to a duty on the Company's part to maintain the confidentiality of such information and to use it only
                    for certain limited purposes. I agree to hold all such confidential or proprietary information in the strictest confidence and not to disclose it to any person, firm or corporation or to use it except as necessary in carrying out my work for the Company consistent with the Company's agreement with such third party.
                </h4>
                <h2 style="color:black;">
                    B) NONCOMPETE COVENANTS
                </h2>
                <h4>
                    It is the Company’s policies to conduct its affairs in strict compliance with the letter and spirit of the law and to adhere to the highest principles of business ethics. Accordingly, all officers, employees, and independent contractors must avoid activities which are in conflict, or give the appearance of being in conflict, with these principles and with the interests of the Company.
                    <p>
                        During the Internship period, I will not, directly or indirectly, work for, own, invest in, direct, or aid any company or person engaged in competition with the Company of <strong>e-Zest Solutions Ltd.</strong> A company or person is in competition with the Company if it solicits business, performs services, or delivers goods that are competitive to the Company, its customers, or its prospective customers. 
                    </p>
                </h4>
                <h2 style="color:black;">
                    E) INVENTIONS AND PROPRIETARY INFORMATION
                </h2>
                <h4>
                    1. I acknowledge that in its business, the Company has developed and commercially used valuable technical and non-technical information and, to protect the legitimate interests of the Company, it is necessary for the Company to protect certain of the information either by patents, copyright, industrial design or by any other available mechanism, or by maintaining the information as secret or confidential.
                    <p>
                        2. I acknowledge that, through my Internship with the Company, I may be exposed to or generate confidential information including, without limiting the generality of the foregoing, technology, know-how, trade secrets, data, processes, inventions, developments, formulations, discoveries, algorithms, applications, methods of manufacture, information pertaining to existing or potential
                        customers, suppliers, markets, contracts, prices, programs, strategies and products, and improvements thereof, whether oral or written, but not including information otherwise publicly known not as a result of a breach of this Agreement, information acquired by me through my own independent research and experience, and information which was lawfully in my possession prior to receipt thereof from the Company. 
                    </p>
                    <p>
                        3. I agree that I shall not disclose to any person, firm or corporation, nor use for my own or another person’s benefit, either during or after my Internship, any confidential information referred to in this agreement, except as otherwise
                        specifically authorised in writing by the Company.
                    </p>
                    <p>
                        4. I will not disclose to the Company or induce the Company to use inventions or confidential information belonging to others.
                    </p>
                    <p>
                        5. I agree to perform for the Company such duties as may be designated from time to time, which may include the functions of inventing, improving, discovering and developing new and novel devices, methods and principles relating to the work of the Company.Any invention, including without limitation, new contributions, concepts, ideas, algorithms, developments, discoveries, processes, compositions, techniques or improvements thereof, made, conceived, learned or reduced to practice during the course of my Internship, and all trade secret, patent, copyright, and other intellectual property rights worldwide therein, are the property of the Company, to which all right, title and interest in and to the same are hereby assigned, whether or not they are patentable or copyrightable or otherwise capable of statutory protection and whether or not they are made by myself or jointly with any other persons. I also hereby waive all moral rights into any copyright assigned hereunder. I also agree to assign all my right, title and
                        interest in and to any such invention to a third party as directed by the Company. I agree that during my Internship by the Company, I will promptly and fully disclose in writing and assign to the Company, all such inventions. I also agree, if requested, to assist the Company or its authorised representative in preparing and obtaining any patents, copyrights, industrial designs or securing any other rights for such inventions, in any and all countries. I also agree, upon request, to execute without further consideration, such documents as may reasonably be required to obtain the patents, copyrights, industrial designs or other rights.  In the event the Company is unable for any reason, after reasonable effort, to secure my signature on any document needed in connection with the actions specified in Sections 5 and 7 hereof, I hereby irrevocably designate and appoint the Company and its duly authorised officers and agents as my agent and attorney in fact, which appointment is coupled with an interest, to act for and in my behalf to execute, verify and file any such documents and to do all other lawfully permitted acts to further the purposes of this Agreement with the same legal force and effect as if executed by me. I hereby waive and quitclaim to the Company any and all claims, of any nature whatsoever, which I now or may hereafter have for infringement of any proprietary rights assigned, hereunder to the Company.
                    </p>
                    <p>
                        6. I agree that, during my Internship, I will not apply for any patent, copyright or industrial design or otherwise secure any other right in any country for any invention, including new contributions, concepts, ideas, algorithms, developments, discoveries, processes, compositions, techniques or improvements thereof, without the prior written consent of the Company. In addition, I will
                        promptly inform the Company of all patent applications filed by me or on my behalf within one year of termination of Internship with sufficient details to enable the Company to reasonably determine that it is not the owner thereof.
                    </p>
                    <p>
                        7. I agree, both during and subsequent to my Internship by the Company, and without any additional compensation other than for out-of-pocket costs incurred, to testify in any legal proceeding, sign all lawful papers, execute all divisional, continuation, substitution, renewal and re-issue applications, execute all assignment papers, make all rightful oaths and generally do everything necessary or desirable to assist the Company or its successors and assigns in obtaining and enforcing proper protection for its patents, copyrights and industrial designs or other relevant rights in any and all countries.
                    </p>
                    <p>
                        8. I agree to make and maintain for the Company, adequate and current written records of all my innovations, inventions, discoveries and improvements.
                    </p>
                    <p>
                        9. I acknowledge that all records or copies of records concerning the Company’s activities, business interest or investigations made or received by me during my Internship with the Company are and shall be the property of the Company. I agree to keep such records or copies in the custody of the Company and subject to its control, and to surrender the same at the termination of my Internship, or at any time during my Internship, at the Company’s request without keeping any copies thereof. Prior to leaving my Internship with the Company, I agree to cooperate with the Company in completing and signing the Company termination statement at the Company’s request. In the event that I leave the employ of the Company, I hereby consent to the notification of my new Company of my rights and obligations under this Agreement.
                    </p>
                    <p>
                        10. I agree to obtain the written consent of the Company in advance of any presentation or publication, or submission for presentation or publication, of any speech, paper or article authored by me, either alone or jointly with others.
                    </p>
                    <p>
                        11. The obligations in agreements shall apply to any period during which I was previously employed, or am in the future employed, by the Company as a consultant if no other agreement governs nondisclosure and assignment of inventions during such period. This Inventions and Proprietary Information Agreement along with the Internship Agreement entered into between me and
                        the Company are the final, complete and exclusive agreement of the parties with respect to the subject matter hereof and supersedes and merges all prior discussions between us. No modification of or amendment to this Invention and Proprietary Information Agreement, nor any waiver of any rights hereunder, will be effective unless in writing and signed by the party to be charged. Any
                        subsequent change or changes in my duties, salary or compensation will not affect the validity or scope of this Agreement.
                    </p>
                </h4>
                <h2 style="color:black;">
                    F) GENERAL PROVISIONS
                </h2>
                <h2 style="color:black;">
                    1) Entire Agreement
                </h2>
                <h4>
                    This Agreement sets forth the entire agreement and understanding between the Company and me relating to the subject matter herein and merges all prior discussions between us. No modification of or amendment to this agreement, nor any waiver of any rights under this agreement, will be effective unless in writing signed by the party to be charged. Any subsequent change or changes in my duties, salary or compensation will not affect the validity or scope of this Agreement.
                </h4>
                <h2 style="color:black;">
                    2) Severability
                </h2>
                <h4>
                    If one or more of the provisions in this Agreement are deemed void by law, then the remaining provisions will continue in full force and effect.
                </h4>
                <h2 style="color:black;">
                    4) Successors and Assigns
                </h2>
                <h4>
                    This Agreement will be binding upon my heirs, executors, administrators and other legal representatives and will be for the benefit of the Company, its successors, and its assigns.
                </h4>
                <h2 class="mt-5">
                    I have read, understood and hereby voluntarily accept the terms of employment outlined
                    above.
                </h2>

<div style="font-size:22px;"><strong>Name:</strong> <span t-field="employee.name"/></div>
<div style="font-size:22px;"><strong>Applicable Date:</strong> <span t-field="employee.joining_date"/></div>
<div style="font-size:22px;"><strong>Signed Date:</strong> <t t-if="employee.nda_signed_off"><span t-field="employee.nda_signed_off"/></t></div>

</div></div>
            </t>
        </t>
    </template>
</odoo>
